

Web developer with 2.6+ years of experience developing responsive and reliable web apps. Typescript, React Js, Next Js, React Native, HTML, and CSS are examples of within-code languages. also experienced with Git, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and Webflow.

Experience



Graphic Designer at Webncos

2019 - 2020



Front End Developer at Webncos.

2020 - current

Education



General Science, Ghana National College

2018 - 2021 ·

code cademy

Front-End Engineer, Codecademy

2018 - 2019 ·

code cademy

Full-Stack Engineer, Codecademy

2019 - 2020 ·

code cademy

React Native And Expo, Codecademy

2020 - 2021 ·

Details

www.iamjulius.com

julius@iamjulius.com (233) 549-321512 linkedin-julius-eghan-4bb7a820a/

Languages

Accra, Ghana

English · Native

Main skills

Team management

Problem solving

Business thinking

Brand strategy

Graphic design

Web development

Mobile App development

Technical skills

UI & UX

Figma And Sketch

HTML & CSS

Tailwind CSS

Typescript

React Native Expo

React Js

Next Js

Git

Vercel

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Webflow